Ellen L. Lutz Papers MS177
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Human rights litigation files, 1957 -- 2004; 1986 -- 1999; MS177.004; 17.35 Linear Feet
  - Ferdinand Marcos, 1962 -- 2004; 1986 -- 1999; MS177.004.002; 13.2 Linear Feet
    - [Sison opening brief and excerpts of record], 1998; MS177.004.002.037.00026 (Box 37)
    - [Annexes], 1998 -- 1999; MS177.004.002.037.00027 (Box 37)
    - Philippine law regarding damages, 1999; MS177.004.002.037.00028 (Box 37)
    - [Settlement hearing] transcript of proceedings, 1999; MS177.004.002.037.00029 (Box 37)
    - Marcos: legal research regarding settlement, 1999; MS177.004.002.037.00030 (Box 37)
    - Marcos: correspondence regarding settlement, 1999; MS177.004.002.037.00031 (Box 37)
    - Marcos: Swift motions regarding settlement, 1999; MS177.004.002.038.00001 (Box 38)
    - Notes from court, 1999; MS177.004.002.038.00002 (Box 38)
    - [Settlement court documents, 1 of 6], 1999; MS177.004.002.038.00003 (Box 38)
    - [Settlement court documents, 2 of 6], 1999; MS177.004.002.038.00004 (Box 38)
    - [Settlement court documents, 3 of 6], 1999; MS177.004.002.038.00005 (Box 38)
    - [Settlement court documents, 4 of 6], 1999; MS177.004.002.038.00006 (Box 38)
    - [Settlement court documents, 5 of 6], 1999; MS177.004.002.038.00007 (Box 38)
    - [Settlement court documents, 6 of 6], 1999; MS177.004.002.038.00008 (Box 38)
    - Marcos endgame, 1999; MS177.004.002.038.00009 (Box 38)
    - [Civil docket, 1 of 2], 1999; MS177.004.002.038.00010 (Box 38)
    - [Civil docket, 2 of 2], 1999; MS177.004.002.038.00011 (Box 38)
    - Marcos - misc., 1998 -- 2000; MS177.004.002.038.00012 (Box 38)
    - [Bibliography and notes], 2004; MS177.004.002.038.00013 (Box 38)
  - Carlos Guillermo Suarez Mason, 1957 -- 1988; 1987 -- 1988; MS177.004.003; 4.15 Linear Feet
    - Statute of limitations - Suarez Mason, 1987; MS177.004.003.031.00029 (Box 31)
    - Statute of limitations, 1957 -- 1980; MS177.004.003.031.00030 (Box 31)
    - Statute of limitations in international law, 1987; MS177.004.003.039.00001 (Box 39)
    - Dickenson, 'The Law of Nations' [and notes], 1981 -- 1987; MS177.004.003.039.00002 (Box 39)
    - [Martinez-Baca v. Suarez Mason complaint], 1987; MS177.004.003.039.00003 (Box 39)
    - [ACLU news release], 1987; MS177.004.003.039.00004 (Box 39)
    - [Rapaport v. Suarez Mason - 1st amended complaint], 1987; MS177.004.003.039.00005 (Box 39)
    - Joinder of indispensible parties, 1987; MS177.004.003.039.00006 (Box 39)
    - Suarez Mason - CCR cases - FOIA requests, 1987; MS177.004.003.039.00007 (Box 39)
    - Conflicts of Laws, 1987; MS177.004.003.039.00008 (Box 39)
    - Forti and Benchoam - Transcript of motion to dismiss proceedings, 1987; MS177.004.003.039.00009 (Box 39)
    - Forti and Benchoam - Decision and order of court, motion to dismiss, 1987; MS177.004.003.039.00010 (Box 39)
    - [Forti and Benchoam v. Suarez Mason - 1st amended complaint], 1987; MS177.004.003.039.00011 (Box 39)
    - Suarez-Mason: Forti and Benchoam - Amnesty International amicus curiae brief, 1987; MS177.004.003.039.00012 (Box 39)
    - Forti and Benchoam - Motion for reconsideration and 2nd amended complaint, 1987; MS177.004.003.039.00013 (Box 39)
    - Forti and Benchoam - 1st amended complaint [empty folder], 1987; MS177.004.003.039.00014 (Box 39)
    - Forti, Benchoam v. Suarez Mason motion to dismiss, 1987; MS177.004.003.039.00015 (Box 39)
    - [Forti and Benchoam - motions], 1987 -- 1988; MS177.004.003.039.00016 (Box 39)
    - [Forti and Benchoam - memorandum regarding February 10th hearings], 1988; MS177.004.003.039.00017 (Box 39)
    - [Forti and Benchoam v. Suarez Mason - deposition of Carlos Guillermo Suarez Mason, Volume 1], 1988; MS177.004.003.039.00018 (Box 39)
    - [Forti and Benchoam v. Suarez Mason - orders], 1988; MS177.004.003.039.00019 (Box 39)
    - Damages [1 of 4], 1987 -- 1988; MS177.004.003.039.00020 (Box 39)
    - Damages [2 of 4], 1988; MS177.004.003.039.00021 (Box 39)
    - Damages [3 of 4], 1982 -- 1988; MS177.004.003.039.00022 (Box 39)
    - Damages [4 of 4], 1988; MS177.004.003.039.00023 (Box 39)
    - Suarez Mason: Extradition [1 of 4], 1988; MS177.004.003.039.00024 (Box 39)
    - Suarez Mason: Extradition [2 of 4], 1987 -- 1988; MS177.004.003.039.00025 (Box 39)
    - Suarez Mason: Extradition [3 of 4], 1987; MS177.004.003.039.00026 (Box 39)
    - Suarez Mason: Extradition [4 of 4], 1986 -- 1987; MS177.004.003.039.00027 (Box 39)
    - [Extradition order], 1988; MS177.004.003.039.00028 (Box 39)
    - Capacity to sue - Suarez Mason, 1984 -- 1988; MS177.004.003.039.00029 (Box 39)
    - Suarez Mason - discovery, 1987 -- 1988; MS177.004.003.039.00030 (Box 39)
    - [Declarations], 1987 -- 1988; MS177.004.003.039.00031 (Box 39)
    - [Notes], 1987 -- 1988; MS177.004.003.039.00032 (Box 39)
    - Rapaport v. Suarez Mason, American Civil Liberties Union V-2, Volume 1, correspondence - clip #1 and #2, 1987 -- 1988; MS177.004.003.039.00033 (Box MS177 Shared 2)
    - Rapaport v. Suarez Mason, American Civil Liberties Union V-2, Volume 2, original and certified papers, 1987 -- 1988; MS177.004.003.039.00034 (Box MS177 Shared 2)
    - Rapaport v. Suarez Mason, American Civil Liberties Union V-2, Volume 2, office memoranda and longhand notes, 1987 -- 1988; MS177.004.003.040.00001 (Box 40)
    - Rapaport v. Suarez Mason, American Civil Liberties Union V-2, Volume 2, memoranda of law, 1985; MS177.004.003.040.00002 (Box 40)
    - Rapaport v. Suarez Mason, American Civil Liberties Union V-2, Volume 2, articles / research, 1987; MS177.004.003.040.00003 (Box 40)
    - Rapaport v. Suarez Mason, American Civil Liberties Union V-2, Volume 2, copies and duplicates [empty folder], 1987; MS177.004.003.040.00004 (Box 40)
    - Rapaport v. Suarez Mason, American Civil Liberties Union V-2, Volume 2, drafts [empty folder], 1987; MS177.004.003.040.00005 (Box 40)
    - Rapaport v. Suarez Mason, American Civil Liberties Union V-2, Volume 2, costs [empty folder], 1987; MS177.004.003.040.00006 (Box 40)
    - Rapaport v. Suarez Mason, American Civil Liberties Union V-2, Volume 2, hold papers, 1987; MS177.004.003.040.00007 (Box 40)
    - Rapaport v. Suarez Mason, American Civil Liberties Union V-2, Volume 2, documents - not originals, 1977 -- 1987; MS177.004.003.040.00008 (Box 40)
    - Rapaport v. Suarez Mason, American Civil Liberties Union V-2, Volume 3.1, court file, court clips #1 and #2 [1 of 3], 1988; MS177.004.003.040.00009 (Box 40)
    - Rapaport v. Suarez Mason, American Civil Liberties Union V-2, Volume 3.1, court file, court clips #1 and #2 [2 of 3], 1987; MS177.004.003.040.00010 (Box 40)
    - Rapaport v. Suarez Mason, American Civil Liberties Union V-2, Volume 3.1, court file, court clips #1 and #2 [3 of 3], 1987 -- 1988; MS177.004.003.040.00011 (Box 40)
    - Rapaport v. Suarez Mason, American Civil Liberties Union V-2, Volume 3.2, court file, court clips #3 and #4 [empty folder], 1988; MS177.004.003.040.00012 (Box 40)
    - [Martinez-Baca v. Suarez Mason - order regarding motion to dismiss and request for a stay], 1988; MS177.004.003.040.00013 (Box 40)
    - Martinez-Baca v. Suarez Mason motion to dismiss, 1988; MS177.004.003.040.00014 (Box 40)
    - Suarez Mason - search for assets, 1988; MS177.004.003.040.00015 (Box 40)
    - [Martinez-Baca - reporter's transcript of proceedings], 1988; MS177.004.003.040.00016 (Box 40)
    - [Declaration of Juan Ernesto Mendez], 1988; MS177.004.003.040.00017 (Box 40)
    - [Rapaport et al. v. Suarez Mason - motion to lift stay and memorandum of points and authorities in support of motion to lift stay], 1988; MS177.004.003.040.00018 (Box 40)
    - [Irell and Manella], 1988; MS177.004.003.040.00019 (Box 40)
    - [Martinez-Baca v. Suarez Mason - correspondence regarding hearing transcript], 1988; MS177.004.003.040.00020 (Box 40)
    - [Memorandum of points and authorities in support of request for damages; proposed judgement], 1988; MS177.004.003.040.00022 (Box 40)
    - [Martinez-Baca v. Suarez Mason - declarations], 1988; MS177.004.003.040.00023 (Box 40)
    - [Rapaport et al v. Suarez Mason - complaints], 1988; MS177.004.003.040.00024 (Box 40)
    - [Rapaport et al v. Suarez Mason - plaintiffs' exhibits, 1 of 5], 1988; MS177.004.003.040.00025 (Box 40)
    - [Rapaport et al v. Suarez Mason - plaintiffs' exhibits, 2 of 5], 1988; MS177.004.003.040.00026 (Box 40)
    - [Rapaport et al v. Suarez Mason - plaintiffs' exhibits, 3 of 5], 1988; MS177.004.003.040.00027 (Box 40)
    - [Rapaport et al v. Suarez Mason - plaintiffs' exhibits, 4 of 5], 1988; MS177.004.003.040.00028 (Box 40)
    - [Rapaport et al v. Suarez Mason - plaintiffs' exhibits, 5 of 5], 1988; MS177.004.003.040.00029 (Box 40)
    - [Notice of related cases], 1988; MS177.004.003.040.00030 (Box 40)
    - Suarez Mason: News clips, 1988; MS177.004.003.040.00031 (Box 40)
    - [Conference calls and news clippings], 1988; MS177.004.003.040.00032 (Box 40)
- Harvard fellowship files, 1956 -- 1998; 1993 -- 1995; MS177.005; 2.4 Linear Feet; 1 Digital Object(s)
  This series consists of case literature, articles and notes. The material supports Lutz's research on "evidentiary problems that arise in the context of accounting for violations of human rights," which she conducted as a fellow at Harvard Law School's Human Rights Program in 1994-1995.
  This series is arranged as received.
  - EALS fellowship, 1995; MS177.005.008.00001 (Box 8)
  - [Research proposal: Proving the Truth], 1994; MS177.005.008.00002 (Box 8)
  - HRP - proposal, 1994; MS177.005.008.00003 (Box 8)
  - Trial of the Argentine generals, 1984 -- 1987; MS177.005.008.00004 (Box 8)
  - D. V. Sandifer, 'Evidence Before International Tribunals', 1975; MS177.005.008.00005 (Box 8)
  - [Amicus curiae brief regarding Argentine tribunals], 1995; MS177.005.008.00006 (Box 8)
  - Command responsibility for HR abuses, EL - 1997, MS177.005.008.00007 (Box 8)
  - [Articles regarding genocide], 1995; MS177.005.008.00008 (Box 8)
  - The Laws of War: Problems of Implementation in Contemporary Conflicts, 1995; MS177.005.008.00009 (Box 8)
  - Orentlicher, 'Settling Accounts', 1991; MS177.005.008.00010 (Box 8)
  - Papers from Harv. Conf. re: sovereignty (belong to K. Sikkink), 1995; MS177.005.008.00011 (Box 8)
  - Tina Rosenberg articles, 1993 -- 1995; MS177.005.008.00012 (Box 8)
  - Kathryn Sikkink articles, 1993 -- 1996; MS177.005.008.00013 (Box 8)
  - International Environmental Law, 1994, MS177.005.008.00014 (Box 8)
  - German reparations law and regs, 1956 -- 1957; MS177.005.008.00015 (Box 8)
  - Medical benefits of receiving reparations, 1965 -- 1990; MS177.005.008.00016 (Box 8)
  - Proposal re: Philippine accountability, 1993; MS177.005.008.00017 (Box 8)
  - Higgins, 'Damage for Violations of One's Human Rights', 1981; MS177.005.008.00018 (Box 8)
  - [News clippings regarding human rights violators], 1989 -- 1991; MS177.005.008.00019 (Box 8)
  - Trials of torturers, 1990; MS177.005.008.00020 (Box 8)
  - Uruguay: The amnesty and plebiscite, 1987 -- 1989; MS177.005.008.00021 (Box 8)
  - Compensation - Japanese Americans, 1987; MS177.005.008.00022 (Box 8)
  - Compensation conference - 3/92, 1992; MS177.005.008.00023 (Box 8)
  - Compensation - misc., 1980 -- 1987; MS177.005.008.00024 (Box 8)
  - Recent Codification of the Law of State Responsibility for Injuries to Aliens, 1974; MS177.005.008.00025 (Box 8)
  - [Suarez-Mason litigation], 1987; MS177.005.008.00026 (Box 8)
  - [Amnesty International reports and notes], 1985 -- 1986; MS177.005.008.00027 (Box 8)
  - Notes re: compensation awarded by U.N. HR committee, 1990; MS177.005.008.00028 (Box 8)
  - German reparations - claims conf., 1990; MS177.005.008.00029 (Box 8)
  - Aspen Institute report re: punishing perpetrators of HR abuses, 1988; MS177.005.008.00030 (Box 8)
  - Therapists' Difficulties in Treating Survivors of the Nazi Holocaust and Their Children, 1981; MS177.005.008.00031 (Box 8)
  - [Literature regarding prosecution of human rights violations and accountability], 1988 -- 1990; MS177.005.008.00032 (Box 8)
  - Nurnberg Trials - 6.F.R.D.69, 1994; MS177.005.008.00033 (Box 8)
  - War crimes tribunal - former Yugoslavia rules of procedures and evidence, 1990; MS177.005.008.00034 (Box 8)
  - Indictments, etc., 1994; MS177.005.008.00035 (Box 8)
  - Ferencz, 'Less Than Slaves', 1974 -- 1995; MS177.005.008.00036 (Box 8)
    This date is approximate
  - [Articles regarding Latin America and U.S. interests], 1988 -- 1994; MS177.005.008.00037 (Box 8)
  - I.A. Norms of Evidence in International Law, 1992 -- 1994; MS177.005.008.00038 (Box 8)
  - I.B. Norms of Evidence in National Tribunals, 1994; MS177.005.008.00039 (Box 8)
  - Rettig Commission (Chile), 1993; MS177.005.008.00040 (Box 8)
  - II.A.1. Argentina - Truth Commission, 1994; MS177.005.008.00041 (Box 8)
  - II.A.2. Truth Commission - Brazil, 1994; MS177.005.008.00042 (Box 8)
  - II.A.3. Truth Commission - Uruguay, 1994; MS177.005.008.00043 (Box 8)
  - II.A.4 Truth Commission - Chile, 1994; MS177.005.008.00044 (Box 8)
  - II.A.5. Truth Commission - El Salvador, 1993; MS177.005.008.00045 (Box 8)
  - II.A.6. Truth Commission - South Africa, 1994 -- 1995; MS177.005.008.00046 (Box 8)
  - II.A.7. Truth Commissions - Other and general articles, 1994; MS177.005.008.00047 (Box 8)
  - II.B.1. Quasi-Truth Commissions - Czechoslovakia, 1994; MS177.005.008.00048 (Box 8)
  - II.B.2. Quasi-Truth Commissions - Hungary, 1994; MS177.005.008.00049 (Box 8)
  - II.B.3. Quasi-Truth Commissions - East Germany, 1994; MS177.005.008.00050 (Box 8)
  - II.B.4. Quasi-Truth Commissions - Poland, 1994; MS177.005.008.00051 (Box 8)
  - II.B.5. Quasi-Truth Commissions - Others, 1994; MS177.005.008.00052 (Box 8)
  - II.C.1. Criminal Prosecution / National Courts - Germany, 1993; MS177.005.008.00053 (Box 8)
  - II.C.2. Criminal Prosecution / National Courts - Greece, 1994; MS177.005.008.00054 (Box 8)
  - II.C.3. Criminal Prosecution / National Courts - Uganda, 1994; MS177.005.008.00055 (Box 8)
  - II.C.4. Criminal Prosecution / National Courts - Argentina, 1988 -- 1995; MS177.005.009.00001 (Box MS177 Shared 8)
  - II.C.5. Criminal Prosecution / National Courts - Chile (letelier), 1994; MS177.005.009.00002 (Box MS177 Shared 8)
  - II.C.6. Criminal Prosecution / National Courts - El Salvador (US nuns), 1994; MS177.005.009.00003 (Box MS177 Shared 8)
  - II.C.7. Criminal Prosecution / National Courts - Ethiopia, 1994; MS177.005.009.00004 (Box MS177 Shared 8)
  - II.C.8. Criminal Prosecution / National Courts - Others, 1994; MS177.005.009.00005 (Box MS177 Shared 8)
  - II.D National Court Civil Proceedings 1. U.S., 1994; MS177.005.009.00006 (Box MS177 Shared 8)
  - II.D.2. Civil Proceedings - National Courts - Europe, 1994; MS177.005.009.00007 (Box MS177 Shared 8)
  - II.D.3. South Korea Civil Proceedings National Courts, 1994; MS177.005.009.00008 (Box MS177 Shared 8)
  - II.D.4. Civil Proceedings - National Courts - other countries, 1994; MS177.005.009.00009 (Box MS177 Shared 8)
  - II.E. Regional Proceedings 1. European Commission and Court, 1994; MS177.005.009.00010 (Box MS177 Shared 8)
  - II.E.2. IACHR and Inter-American Court, 1992 -- 1993; MS177.005.009.00011 (Box MS177 Shared 8)
  - II.E.3. CSCE, 1994; MS177.005.009.00012 (Box MS177 Shared 8)
  - II.F.1 HR Committee, 1991; MS177.005.009.00013 (Box MS177 Shared 8)
  - II.F.2. Special Rapporteurs, 1994; MS177.005.009.00014 (Box MS177 Shared 8)
  - II.F.3. other special procedures established by UN, 1994; MS177.005.009.00015 (Box MS177 Shared 8)
  - II.G.1. Nuremberg, 1994; MS177.005.009.00016 (Box MS177 Shared 8)
  - III.A. Burden of Proof, 1990; MS177.005.009.00017 (Box MS177 Shared 8)
  - III.B. Hearsay, 1994; MS177.005.009.00018 (Box MS177 Shared 8)
  - III.C. Pattern and Practice, 1994; MS177.005.009.00019 (Box MS177 Shared 8)
  - III.D. Expert Testimony, 1994; MS177.005.009.00020 (Box MS177 Shared 8)
  - III.E. Weighting Evidence, 1994; MS177.005.009.00021 (Box MS177 Shared 8)
  - III.F. Immunity from Prosecution, 1994; MS177.005.009.00022 (Box MS177 Shared 8)
  - GR, Use of Medical Science in Protecting HR in the 21st Century, 1992; MS177.005.009.00023 (Box MS177 Shared 8)
  - IV.A. DNA/HLA, 1994 -- 1995; MS177.005.009.00024 (Box MS177 Shared 8)
  - IV.B. Other Bio-Chemical Tests (eg. brain chemical alteration), 1995; MS177.005.009.00025 (Box MS177 Shared 8)
  - IV.C. Diagnostic Imaging, 1994; MS177.005.009.00026 (Box MS177 Shared 8)
  - IV.D.1. PTSD (Psychological interference with memory / ability to testify), 1994; MS177.005.009.00027 (Box MS177 Shared 8)
  - IV.D.2. Recovered Memory (Psychological interference with memory), 1993 -- 1995; MS177.005.009.00028 (Box MS177 Shared 8)
  - IV.E. Cultural Interference with Memory / Ability to Testify, 1994; MS177.005.009.00029 (Box MS177 Shared 8)
  - Amnesties, 1994; MS177.005.009.00030 (Box MS177 Shared 8)
  - Reparations for African-American slavery, 1994; MS177.005.009.00031 (Box MS177 Shared 8)
  - IELTRUTH, WP 5.1, Materials related to evidence study, 1998-02-05; MS177.005.009.00083
- Fletcher and the Center for Human Rights and Conflict Resolution files, 1991 -- 2003; 1995 -- 2002; MS177.006; 3.6 Linear Feet; 16 Digital Object(s)
  This series contains course material and working files of Lutz from her time at the Fletcher School and the Center for Human Rights and Conflict Resolution (CHRCR), dating from 1997 through 2004. The bulk of the series consists of lecture notes, reading lists and syllabi from courses taught by Lutz at Tufts. A few folders and electronic files contain CHRCR material, which includes correspondence planning the establishment of the Center in 2000. Ongoing projects that Lutz worked on while at Fletcher, but that extend beyond her time there, are located in Series 8 (Projects and subject files).
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  - Appointment letter - Political Science, Tufts University, 1996; MS177.006.020.00018 (Box MS177 Shared 6)
  - [CHRCR] annotated bibliography, 2002 -- 2003; MS177.006.020.00019 (Box MS177 Shared 6)
  - CHRCR database - Ellen's copy, 2000; MS177.006.020.00020 (Box MS177 Shared 6)
  - CHRCR files - I, sept 02 - july 10, 2003, 2002 -- 2003; MS177.006.020.00021 (Box MS177 Shared 6)
  - CHRCR files - II, sept 02 - july 10, 2003, 2002 -- 2003; MS177.006.020.00022 (Box MS177 Shared 6)
  - CHRCR initial conference reports: 1. Fletcher, Dec 2000; 2. Talloires May 2001, 2000 -- 2001; MS177.006.020.00023 (Box MS177 Shared 6)
  - [CHRCR unlabeled floppy disk], 2003; MS177.006.020.00024 (Box MS177 Shared 6)
  - [Course nomination], 2002; MS177.006.020.00025 (Box MS177 Shared 6)
  - Fletcher contract, 1996 -- 2000; MS177.006.020.00026 (Box MS177 Shared 6)
  - Fletcher School lecture 6/95 [and Fletcher job offer], 1995; MS177.006.020.00027 (Box MS177 Shared 6)
  - Fletcher / Tufts Ks and grads [Fletcher and CHRCR job offers], 1998 -- 2001; MS177.006.020.00028 (Box MS177 Shared 6)
  - Fletcher / Tufts Ks and grads: Law 260 Moot court problem, spring 1999, MS177.006.020.00029 (Box MS177 Shared 6)
  - Fletcher / Tufts Ks and grads: Model UN - International Organization, 1999; MS177.006.020.00030 (Box MS177 Shared 6)
  - Fletcher / Tufts Ks and grads: Summer 98 - Grades, Talloires [1 of 2], 1998; MS177.006.020.00031 (Box MS177 Shared 6)
  - Fletcher / Tufts Ks and grads: Summer 98 - Grades, Talloires [2 of 2]: ['Tufts Summer Programs in the French Alps' VHS], 1998; MS177.006.020.00032 (Box MS177 Shared 6)
  - Tufts Political Science department, Human Rights course, Winter 96, 1996; MS177.006.020.00033 (Box MS177 Shared 6)
  - International Criminal Court Colombia exercise, 2002; MS177.006.020.00034 (Box MS177 Shared 6)
  - International Criminal Court meeting - Rome, 1998; MS177.006.020.00035 (Box MS177 Shared 6)
  - United States responses to International Criminal Court, 2002; MS177.006.020.00036 (Box MS177 Shared 6)
  - International Criminal Tribunal for Rwanda - Akayesu, 1998; MS177.006.020.00037 (Box MS177 Shared 6)
  - International Criminal Law and the International Criminal Court, loose material, 1 of 13], 1998 -- 2002; MS177.006.020.00038 (Box MS177 Shared 6)
  - International Criminal Law and the International Criminal Court, loose material, 2 of 13], 1999 -- 2002; MS177.006.020.00039 (Box MS177 Shared 6)
  - International Criminal Law and the International Criminal Court, loose material, 3 of 13], 2000 -- 2001; MS177.006.020.00040 (Box MS177 Shared 6)
  - International Criminal Law and the International Criminal Court, loose material, 4 of 13], 1998 -- 2002; MS177.006.020.00041 (Box MS177 Shared 6)
  - International Criminal Law and the International Criminal Court, loose material, 5 of 13], 1995 -- 1998; MS177.006.020.00042 (Box MS177 Shared 6)
  - International Criminal Law and the International Criminal Court, loose material, 6 of 13], 1994 -- 2002; MS177.006.041.00001 (Box 41)
  - International Criminal Law and the International Criminal Court, loose material, 7 of 13], 1991 -- 2001; MS177.006.041.00002 (Box 41)
  - International Criminal Law and the International Criminal Court, loose material, 8 of 13], 1998; MS177.006.041.00003 (Box 41)
  - International Criminal Law and the International Criminal Court, loose material, 9 of 13], 1995 -- 1998; MS177.006.041.00004 (Box 41)
  - International Criminal Law and the International Criminal Court, loose material, 10 of 13], 1995 -- 2001; MS177.006.041.00005 (Box 41)
  - International Criminal Law and the International Criminal Court, loose material, 11 of 13], 1999 -- 2002; MS177.006.041.00006 (Box 41)
  - International Criminal Law and the International Criminal Court, loose material, 12 of 13], 1996 -- 2002; MS177.006.041.00007 (Box 41)
  - International Criminal Law and the International Criminal Court, loose material, 13 of 13], 1997 -- 2001; MS177.006.041.00008 (Box 41)
  - International Criminal Law, Teacher's Manual, 2001; MS177.006.041.00009 (Box 41)
  - Justice Goldstone visit, 1997; MS177.006.041.00010 (Box 41)
  - [LAW209: International Human Rights Law] Fall 1995 - teaching evaluations, 1997; MS177.006.041.00011 (Box 41)
  - [LAW209: International Human Rights Law] student evaluations, 1995; MS177.006.041.00012 (Box 41)
  - [LAW209: International Human Rights Law], 1995; MS177.006.041.00013 (Box 41)
  - [LAW209: International Human Rights Law], 1995 -- 1996; MS177.006.041.00014 (Box 41)
  - [LAW209: International Human Rights Law], 1996; MS177.006.041.00015 (Box 41)
  - [LAW210: International Organizations], 1996; MS177.006.041.00016 (Box 41)
  - [LAW210: International Organizations], 1996 -- 1998; MS177.006.041.00017 (Box 41)
  - [LAW210] International Organizations 98 lecture notes, 1998; MS177.006.041.00018 (Box 41)
  - LAW211: Human Righs Law Seminar lecture notes, spring 1996, MS177.006.041.00019 (Box 41)
  - [LAW211: Seminar on Current Issues in Human Rights] Teaching evaluations, spring 1996, MS177.006.041.00020 (Box 41)
  - [LAW213: International Criminal Law], 2002; MS177.006.041.00021 (Box 41)
  - [Law213] International Criminal Law [1 of 2], 2002; MS177.006.041.00022 (Box 41)
  - [Law213] International Criminal Law [2 of 2], 2002; MS177.006.041.00023 (Box 41)
  - LAW213: International Criminal Law, spring 2002 [reader], MS177.006.042.00001 (Box 42)
  - [LAW213] Misc. International Criminal Law readings [1 of 2], 2002; MS177.006.042.00002 (Box 42)
  - [LAW213] Misc. International Criminal Law readings [2 of 2], 2002; MS177.006.042.00003 (Box 42)
  - [LAW260: International Criminal Law, lecture notes], 1997; MS177.006.042.00004 (Box 42)
  - [LAW260] International Criminal Law reader I, spring 1997 [1 of 4], MS177.006.042.00005 (Box 42)
  - [LAW260] International Criminal Law reader I, spring 1997 [2 of 4], MS177.006.042.00006 (Box 42)
  - [LAW260] International Criminal Law reader I, spring 1997 [3 of 4], MS177.006.042.00007 (Box 42)
  - [LAW260] International Criminal Law reader I, spring 1997 [4 of 4], MS177.006.042.00008 (Box 42)